Mr.
Wu is telling the students how to get along with friends.
Listen to him and complete the notes below. Hello students!
I'm going to give you some tips on how to get along with your friends.
First, be a good listener.
It's important to get to know your friends well, so listen to them.
You can ask questions to show that you're interested in what they're saying.
Body language can also help show that you're listening.
Try to look at your friends when they're talking, and nod your head from time to time.
Second, be a cheerful person.
When you're with friends, focus on the good things in life.
Share funny stories and happy experiences with them.
It's also good to notice and care about your friends' feelings, so you can help them if they feel bad.
A good friend makes you happy and cheers you up when you feel down.
Friendships are a treasure in our life, and everybody should know how to keep their friendships strong and healthy.